<resources>
    <string name="app_name">tadallal</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email Address</string>
    <string name="password">password</string>
    <string name="did_you_forget_your_password">Forgot Password ?</string>
    <string name="create_new_account">Create New Account</string>
    <string name="register_new_account">Create New Account</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="country">Country</string>
    <string name="user_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="retrive_account_information">Retrieve Your Account</string>
    <string name="retrive">Retrieve</string>
    <string name="about_us1">FOR US, IT IS NOT JUST ABOUT DELIVERING YOUR ORDER, BUT IT IS ACOMMUNICATION CHANNEL THAT ALWAYS MEETS YOUR NEEDS .</string>
    <string name="about_us2">* The first and only application in Kuwait that provides a unique and distinctive service to customers, including a refund of 10% of the value of your purchases on each order you order from our website through the cashback program, which is automatically refunded to the customer’s digital wallet, in addition to other offers and discounts.
*Tadallal … is the service of ordering food, flowers, sweets, cocoa, pharmacies, associations, perfumes, clothes and out lit, as there are many other participating commercial companies…
tadallal everything you want to order online…..
* It is the fastest and easiest way to help you get your order from places near your area and choose what you need according to the type of order you want to order</string>
    <string name="about_us3">*Tadallal is an electronic application in which you enjoy every day, upon request, the daily offers and discounts offered by thousands of companies, restaurants, fashion, perfumes, flowers, associations, pharmacies, Outlet and other sections that participate with us on the application …
** Ask from Tadallal to get the best offers and services, and 10% of your purchases will be refunded directly to your wallet. You can use it as you wish.</string>
    <string name="about_us_title1">ALL YOU WANT BY ONE CLICK</string>
    <string name="about_us_title2">WHAT IS APPLICATION tadallal…?</string>
    <string name="about_us_title3">WHY tadallal…?</string>
    <string name="www_alshal_sa">www.tadallal.sa</string>
    <string name="saudi_arabia_jeddah_966_12_600000_ext_3101_info_alshal_sa">Saudi Arabia, Jeddah +966 12 600000 Ext 3101 info@tadallal.sa</string>
    <string name="about_app">About App</string>
    <string name="main">Main</string>
    <string name="my_account">My Account</string>
    <string name="favourit">Favourite</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="or">Or</string>
    <string name="add_address">Add address</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name *</string>
    <string name="country_">Country*</string>
    <string name="city_">City*</string>
    <string name="neighborhood_name">Neighborhood name*</string>
    <string name="street_name">Street Name*</string>
    <string name="postal_code">Postal number</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone number*</string>
    <string name="continue_">Continue</string>
    <string name="back">back</string>
    <string name="_966">966+</string>
    <string name="ryal">KW</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="style">Style</string>
    <string name="color">Color</string>
    <string name="cloth">Cloth</string>
    <string name="arm_type">Arm type</string>
    <string name="size_">Size</string>
    <string name="clarify_the_size_chart">Clarify the size chart</string>
    <string name="add_to_cart">Add to cart</string>
    <string name="delivery_addresses">Delivery_addresses</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="choose">choose</string>
    <string name="size_table">Size Table</string>
    <string name="sizing_chart_video">Sizing chart video</string>
    <string name="all_dimensions_are_taken_in_inches">All dimensions are taken in inches</string>
    <string name="sleeve_aperture_depending_on_the_model">Sleeve aperture depending on the model</string>
    <string name="sleeve_size_from_the_beginning_of_the_shoulder">The sleeve fits from the beginning of the shoulder*</string>
    <string name="shopping_basket">Shopping basket</string>
    <string name="complete_the_request">Complete order</string>
    <string name="continue_shopping">Continue shopping</string>
    <string name="there_are_no_product_in_cart">There are no products in the cart</string>
    <string name="quntity">Quantity:</string>
    <string name="change_language">change Language</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="delivery_address">Delivery Address:</string>
    <string name="payment_method">Payment method:</string>
    <string name="confirm_order">Confirm order</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="use">Use</string>
    <string name="total">Total</string>
    <string name="delivery">delivery</string>
    <string name="taxes">taxes</string>
    <string name="final_total">Total</string>
    <string name="paying_off">Paying</string>
    <string name="abayas_occasions">Abayas occasions</string>
    <string name="discount_section">Discount section %</string>
    <string name="main_page">Main page</string>
    <string name="order_history">Order history</string>
    <string name="about_us_">About us</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="change_language_">Change language</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="ther_is_no_data_to_show">No Data To Show</string>
    <string name="add_new_address">Add New Address</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="profile_info">Personal profile</string>
    <string name="orders">Orders</string>
    <string name="account_info">Account info</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit profile</string>
    <string name="search_about_specific_product">Search for a specific product</string>
    <string name="terms_and_condirions_text">These terms and conditions govern the users of the tadallal website. Accordingly, these terms and conditions were formed a binding agreement between both the first party as a user of the site and the second party (tadallal). When using the site, the first party agrees to abide by these terms and any additions or modifications to them. Therefore, we ask you to read these terms and conditions very carefully before using the site. We also draw your attention to the fact that these terms and conditions do not constitute undeclared relations between both the site and its users.
The user of this website is subject to the privacy policy. Therefore, we ask you to carefully review the privacy policy of the site before using it. The provisions of the Privacy Policy are considered in effect in the event of any conflict between each of the provisions that fall under these terms and conditions and provisions under the Privacy Policy\n\n

These conditions are in effect for the user who is in any of the European Union countries. This agreement guarantees the delivery of products or services via tadallal, according to the payment method used to purchase the products or services. These terms are an agreement between both parties. In the event that the user of the website is present in any other countries, and Morgan Saudi Arabia will deliver any of the products or services to him directly\n\n

<b>1.</b> Acceptance of terms of service and modifications: The user of the tadallal site is considered bound by these terms and conditions or any amendments made to them from time to time without informing him at any time of using the site. In addition, if a specific service is used or accessed through the tadallal site, it is The user is subject to any applicable rules or guidelines for these services and will be referred to in these terms of service. Please read the website privacy policy carefully, which is listed under these terms and conditions\n\n

<b>2.</b> tadallal website services The tadallal website and the services provided through it have a “premium service” policy. tadallal reserves the right to amend or disable the site’s provisions and services and delete user data temporarily or permanently at any time without informing the user, and the site’s management disclaims its responsibility for that. The site does not bear any responsibility for the direction of the appropriate timing, removal of data, lack of storage, accuracy of information or inappropriate delivery.\n\n

<b>3.</b> User responsibility and registration obligations A user must have a user account on the tadallal site when interacting with the site. In this case, proper data must be used - if the minimum age is required for the user\'s account - the user must be at least the required age. Registering for a user account on the site is considered a clear agreement to the terms and conditions of the site, including any modifications made by the site, which are published here.\n\n

<b>4.</b> Privacy Policy The registration data and other personal data obtained by the site are considered as the terms of the privacy policy of tadallal site\n\n

<b>5.</b> Registration and Password Here the user is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of his password and for any use of the user’s account or his username, whether with or without permission from the user, the user informs the site immediately upon unauthorized use of the account or the username. Or its password\n\n

<b>6.</b> Product return or exchange policy If the user is not satisfied with the purchase, please contact sales@tadallal.sa within 5 days of receiving the product, to arrange a refund or exchange. The integrity of the products is required upon delivery, provided that they are in their original condition and are not used, washed, or have undergone a change, in addition to preserving their integrity from any damage, and that the original marks are attached to them and the product package is attached.\n\n

<b>7.</b> User Behavior The user or any person who manages his account shall be responsible for all data and information of any kind, whether text, programs, symbols, music, sounds, pictures, graphics, videos, or other materials and make them available publicly or privately. The site can display inappropriate user content, and the site does not bear any responsibility for error or negligence for the direction of the content displayed on its page. The use of the tadallal site or any of its services is considered a clear agreement about: - The user does not add any content or act in a way that is interpreted as not Legal, illegal, threatening, harmful, abusive, terrorist, vulgar, offensive, pornographic or indecent, which may aim to interfere with the site’s policy or any of its provided services or aim to harm or destroy programming routine, which may lead to civil and criminal liability Or a violation of applicable international, national or local laws. - The user does not impersonate or misrepresent any person or entity associated with it, and the user does not seek to hide or change the origin of any content that he displays. - The user does not collect data from other users- The user does not use the content or services of the site commercially, or in any way that uses junk mail, spam, chain letters, pyramid schemes, or any form of advertisement or unannounced trade. The user of the site does not promote or operate any service or content without the prior written consent of the site administration. - The user undertakes not to provide any content that would expose the site to civil or criminal accountability or violate any of the international, local or national laws. To mention but not limited to copyright, trademark, patent or trade secret laws.\n\n

<b>8.</b>     tadallal site content When adding content to the site, the following is required: A- The user of the tadallal site grants the rights to display and copyright only to us, and we do not give the right to anyone to use any images or content within the site for external publishing for his account and we have full ownership rights for Brand tadallal b- The user undertakes With his full legal and moral rights, through which he can grant the site the aforementioned license as described in Clause 7.\n\n

<b>9.</b> Typographical errors: Although tadallal is keen to present elaborate products and pricing data, it is possible to make typographical errors or pricing errors. The site administration cannot confirm the price of the product except after the user has requested. In the event that the product is included in the incorrect price list or incorrect data due to a mistake in the product\'s pricing or data, then the site management has the freedom to act on its own to reject or cancel any purchases that included that product. If the product price is not included for a defect, the site management has the freedom to act either to contact the user for clarification or cancel the user\'s request and inform him of the process of canceling the purchase\n\n

<b>10.</b> Currency rates: The process of determining the prices of tadallal products is based on the Saudi Riyal\n\n

<b>11.</b> Compensation: The user shall indemnify tadallal website, its representatives, its affiliates, its related parties, its employees, directors, its officials, its clients, independent contractors, advertisers, partners and trademark partners, and pay the damages against him against any claim or claim that includes the payment of reasonable legal fees that may be submitted by any A third party as a result of the user’s behavior, his dealings with the site or any of its services, the provision of the user’s content, the user’s failure to adhere to these terms and conditions, or any other violations that the user takes against the rights of any person or other party.\n\n

<b>12.</b> Disclaimer The user acknowledges and assumes full responsibility for the use of the tadallal website; And any of its services or content. The site’s services and content are subject to a “as is” policy, and the site waives all guarantees of any kind, whether implicit or declared, which include, for example, but not limited to, the guarantee of popularity, suitability for a specific purpose, and non-infringement. The site does not explicitly or implicitly guarantee the interruption of any part of its services, freedom from errors, exposure to viruses, time commitment, security, accuracy, liability, or any other quality guarantee. The site does not guarantee publicly or implicitly that any content will be saved through any of the download methods. The user acknowledges that the site or any of its service employees do not provide any kind of advice or information that the site’s management possesses, and the user bears full responsibility for their use, and the site’s management disclaims its full responsibility for that. Some jurisdictions do not allow disclaimers of implicit representations. Some of the statements in the above statement of liability may not apply to the user with respect to the implied undertakings, however other terms and conditions remain enforceable.\n\n

<b>13.</b> Limitation of liability: The user acknowledges that the editors of the site are not responsible for any direct, indirect, special, accidental or consequential damage. For example, but not limited to, the damages include the loss of profits, good reputation, use, data, or tangible losses (even if notified The site is subject to potential harm (resulting from: - Use of services or the inability to use them). The cost of owning alternative products or services resulting from any transaction concluded through the services. - Unauthorized access or alteration of the transfer of user data. Permissions or any third party\'s use of services. Any other matters related to the services. Some jurisdictions refuse to limit liability and thus these restrictions may not apply to the user.\n\n

<b>14.</b> Protection of rights: The management of the site owns all rights, which include - but not limited to - copyrights, trademarks, patents, trade secrets or any other property rights owned by tadallal belonging to the site and its content, products and services. Use of website rights and ownership requires the website\'s prior written consent. The management of the tadallal website does not guarantee explicit or implicit licenses or rights when making its services available, and the user does not have any authority to conduct a commercial transaction through the tadallal site or use its services without obtaining the prior written consent of the site.\n\n

<b>15.</b> Copyright Infringement and Copyright If the user doubts that his property is infringing on his rights, he can contact the Copyright Agent on the tadallal website using the following mail: info@tadallal.sa\n\n

<b>16.</b> Dispute Resolution In the event that the parties are unable to resolve a dispute between them within 30 days of the occurrence of the dispute, all parties shall submit the dispute to the commercial courts in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia or the authority that has jurisdiction under the regulations and decisions in force in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia according to the laws of the committees Arbitration is effective at the time the request for arbitration is submitted. Arbitration decisions are final and binding on both parties\n\n

<b>17.</b> Miscellaneous: - In the event that any of the provisions of these terms and conditions conflict with rulings issued by a court against any of the parties, the aforementioned judgment shall be interpreted according to what is reflected in the original intentions of both parties, according to the laws in effect. The rest of these terms and conditions will be applicable and valid as well - the failure of either party to prove any rights under these terms and conditions will not be considered a waiver of the right of that party and the said right will remain fully valid - the user acknowledges that any lawsuit or case For tadallal or any of its services, it must be within six months of its filing, otherwise the lawsuit or the aforementioned case will be stopped forever without consideration for any legislation in violation - tadallal will set the rights and obligations of the site under these terms and conditions and then tadallal will be exempt from any additional obligations\n\n

<b>18.</b> Delivery and shipping clause: - In the event of delivery within the city of Jeddah, the expected time for the arrival of the product is 10 working days. - In the event that outside the city of Jeddah, shipment is through the shipping companies indicated in the choice of shipment and this is available for the customer\'s choice of the expected time for the arrival of the product from two to four working days. According to the policy and conditions of the shipping company’s delivery, we are not responsible for any delay caused by the shipping company\n\n

    \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="Register_successfully">Registered Successfully</string>
    <string name="welcome_tex">You can now complete your order and buy the products you want</string>
    <string name="please_enter_fullname">Please enter the name</string>
    <string name="please_enter_phone_number">Please enter your mobile number</string>
    <string name="please_enter_country">Please enter the country</string>
    <string name="please_enter_city">Please enter your city</string>
    <string name="please_enter_ىeighborhood_name">Please enter the neighborhood name</string>
    <string name="please_enter_street_name">Please enter the street name</string>
    <string name="please_enter_postal_number">Please enter the postal number </string>
    <string name="add_address_completed_successfully">Address added successfully</string>
    <string name="size_1">Size 1</string>
    <string name="size_2">Size 2</string>
    <string name="size_3">Size 3</string>
    <string name="please_enter_your_quantity">Please enter the quantity you want to add</string>
    <string name="your_request_addeed_to_cart_successfully">Your request has been added to the cart successfully</string>
    <string name="delete_product">Delete product</string>
    <string name="delete_product_cart">Are you sure to delete this product !!</string>
    <string name="yes">yse</string>
    <string name="no">no</string>
    <string name="please_enter_copoun_code">Please enter the discount code </string>
    <string name="Saudi">Saudi</string>
    <string name="please_enter_email_address">Please enter the email</string>
    <string name="please_enter_your_country">Please choose your country</string>
    <string name="please_enter_password">Please enter a password </string>
    <string name="please_enter_confirm_password"> Please enter confirm password</string>
    <string name="sorry_your_password_dose_not_match">Password does not match</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_to_logout">Are you sure to log out?</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="this_product_already_in_fav">This product is already in the favorites</string>
    <string name="product_addd_to_favourite">The product has been added to your favorites</string>
    <string name="egypt">Egypt</string>
    <string name="your_account_edited_successfully">Your profile has been modified successfully</string>
    <string name="please_choose_your_language">Please Choose Your language</string>
    <string name="create_new_account_">Create New Account</string>
    <string name="search_for_product">Search for a specific product</string>
    <string name="open_order_details">Order Details</string>
    <string name="order">Order</string>
    <string name="shippment_details">Shipment Info:</string>
    <string name="shipment_number">Shipment number:</string>
    <string name="your_order_completed_successfully">Your request has been successfully completed</string>
    <string name="wrong_email_or_password">Wrong password or email address</string>
    <string name="promo_code_added">Promo Code Added Successfully</string>
    <string name="there_is_no_product_with_this_name">There is no product with this name</string>
    <string name="please_enter_search_word">Please Enter Your Search Word</string>
    <string name="product_removed_fav_successfully">Product removed Successfully</string>
    <string name="redo_order">Redo Order</string>
    <string name="address_deleted_successfully">Address Deleted Successfully</string>
    <string name="please_enter_valid_email">Please Enter A Valid Email Address</string>
    <string name="the_password_sent_to_mailbox">The password has been sent to your mailbox</string>
    <string name="height">Height</string>
    <string name="overall_width">Overall width</string>
    <string name="the_waist">The waist</string>
    <string name="sleeve">Sleeve</string>
    <string name="klush">Klush</string>
    <string name="how_to_take_measurements">How to take measurements</string>
    <string name="additional_requests">Additional requests</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="customize_your_sizes">Customize your sizes</string>
    <string name="promo_code">Promo Code</string>
    <string name="best_selling">Best Selling</string>
    <string name="recently_added">Recently Added</string>
    <string name="agree_to_the_terms_and_conditions">Agree to the terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="please_agree_for_terms">Please Agree For The Terms And Conditions</string>
    <string name="logout_successfully">LogOut Successfully</string>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="quntity1">Quantity</string>
    <string name="order_details">Order Details</string>
    <string name="please_complete_order_details">Please Complete Your Order Details</string>
    <string name="please_enter_length">Please Enter Your Order Length</string>
    <string name="please_enter_kalush">Please Enter Your Order Kalosh</string>
    <string name="please_enter_width">Please Enter Your Order Width</string>
    <string name="please_enter_sleeve">Please Enter Your Order Sleeve</string>
    <string name="please_enter_waist">Please Enter Your Order Waist</string>
    <string name="naighbour_">neighborhood </string>
    <string name="streat">street </string>
    <string name="post_code">Postal code </string>
    <string name="deleviry_address">Delivery_address:</string>
    <string name="Lenght">Length</string>
    <string name="customize">Customize :</string>
    <string name="chat_with_us">Chat with us</string>
    <string name="type_a_message">Type a message ...</string>
    <string name="how_can_we_help_you">how can we help you ?</string>
    <string name="please_enter_your_message">Please enter your message</string>
    <string name="customer_care_whatsapp">Customer Care WhatsApp</string>
    <string name="start_live_chat">Start Live Chat</string>
    <string name="call_customer_care">Call Customer Care</string>
    <string name="send_an_email">Send an Email</string>
    <string name="faqs">FAQs</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="instgram">Instagram</string>
    <string name="snapchat">SnapChat</string>
    <string name="shops">Shops</string>
    <string name="offers">Offers</string>
    <string name="Color">Color</string>
</resources>